<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>cheetahtec@gmail.com</author>
  <authoruserid>ec4c2dd5-055d-44e0-8635-4a4ccfc80e49</authoruserid>
  <initialImageUrl>/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f04%2f6939663665_614aa912ed_b.jpg.axdx</initialImageUrl>
  <mainImageUrl>/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f04%2fCharllotesville+Derby+Dames.jpg.axdx</mainImageUrl>
  <title>Want to Be Featured?</title>
  <description />
  <content>Each week, Rollin' News likes to put a spotlight on the leagues and skaters of Roller Derby.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Right now, if you didn't know it, there are just over 50,000 skaters in the world of Derby as well as over &lt;a href="http://derbyroster.com/"&gt;1,500 leagues&lt;/a&gt; give or take. &amp;nbsp;We know these numbers aren't entirely accurate, but its the best we can do to assume how many Roller Derby leagues there are in the world. &amp;nbsp;If you do some math for active skaters, 30 * 1,500 = 45,000 give or take several thousand due to larger and smaller leagues. &amp;nbsp;Those numbers are promising, because it shows derby is growing. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;With all that derby going on in the world, we believe that every derby player and league need some recognition. &amp;nbsp;So we setup our front page of Rollin News to give you just that! &amp;nbsp;Each week at random, a league and player are chosen from our collective database with &lt;a href="https://rdnation.com/"&gt;RDNation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and then put up front and center on the very page over &lt;b&gt;22,000&lt;/b&gt; people visit each month.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Therefore, we wanted to let you know what it takes to be featured as well as what we display and why.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Featured Leagues&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;In order to be a featured league, we require the following:&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your league must be apart of RDNation. &amp;nbsp;Your league doesn't have to pay to be featured.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your league has more than five members on RDNation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your logo is uploaded on RDNation. &amp;nbsp;We can't show you off without that logo.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your website needs to be filled in too!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So what do we show off to the world?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;The league name.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The league logo.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The city and state.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The leagues website address.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your &lt;a href="https://shops.rdnation.com/"&gt;shop and merchandise&lt;/a&gt;. (If your league has one with RDNation)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Your Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter. (If they are filled out on RDNation)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So go get your league started on &lt;a href="https://rdnation.com/"&gt;RDNation&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;You don't need to be using RDNation or their services in order to get featured. &amp;nbsp;So what are you waiting for?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;b&gt;Feature Skater&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We ask the same things from you in order to be picked as a featured skater.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;You must have an active profile on RDNation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You shouldn't be retired on your profile.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You must have uploaded your profile picture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You must have both a player # and derby name filled out.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No private profiles of RDNation will be featured. &amp;nbsp;If you hid your profile, it will not be featured.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You must have a bio filled out. &amp;nbsp;No matter how short or long, there must be something you typed in for your profile. &amp;nbsp;But please keep it clean. &amp;nbsp;One of the profiles we had didn't have such a clean bio and we had to remove them from being featured.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;So go get a profile on &lt;a href="https://rdnation.com/"&gt;RDNation&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;Did we mention, that the profile you create can also be used to login to Rollin' News? &amp;nbsp;You can have one login, but it works across sites!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;We ask you to sign up to &lt;a href="https://rdnation.com/"&gt;RDNation&lt;/a&gt; because we do our best to automate the entire process of featured leagues and skaters. &amp;nbsp;While we could input them manually, it would take more time out of our day. &amp;nbsp;Time that is used to create a better community for derby world wide.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;* "Abs of Steel, lead jammer and MVP" by &lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/24oranges/"&gt;24oranges.nl&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;* "5th Annual Holiday Heritage Parade in Charlottesville" by &lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/small_realm/"&gt;Bob Mical&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-04-06 01:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-04-04 10:00:15</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>want-to-be-featured</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>Rollin News</tag>
    <tag>RDNation</tag>
    <tag>Skaters</tag>
    <tag>Leagues</tag>
    <tag>Charlottesville Derby Dames</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>3230445c-ecc1-4044-8f76-9f9a17673967</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>