<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>cheetahtec@gmail.com</author>
  <authoruserid>ec4c2dd5-055d-44e0-8635-4a4ccfc80e49</authoruserid>
  <initialImageUrl>/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f08%2fzebracolored.jpg.axdx</initialImageUrl>
  <mainImageUrl>/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f08%2fColoredTransitions.jpg.axdx</mainImageUrl>
  <title>Meecher MKR - Roller Derby As Religion And The Birth Of  The Derby Saints</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;!--[if gte mso 9]&gt;&lt;xml&gt;
 &lt;w:WordDocument&gt;
  &lt;w:View&gt;Normal&lt;/w:View&gt;
  &lt;w:Zoom&gt;0&lt;/w:Zoom&gt;
  &lt;w:PunctuationKerning&gt;&lt;/w:PunctuationKerning&gt;
  &lt;w:ValidateAgainstSchemas&gt;&lt;/w:ValidateAgainstSchemas&gt;
  &lt;w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;false&lt;/w:SaveIfXMLInvalid&gt;
  &lt;w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;false&lt;/w:IgnoreMixedContent&gt;
  &lt;w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;false&lt;/w:AlwaysShowPlaceholderText&gt;
  &lt;w:Compatibility&gt;
   &lt;w:BreakWrappedTables&gt;&lt;/w:BreakWrappedTables&gt;
   &lt;w:SnapToGridInCell&gt;&lt;/w:SnapToGridInCell&gt;
   &lt;w:WrapTextWithPunct&gt;&lt;/w:WrapTextWithPunct&gt;
   &lt;w:UseAsianBreakRules&gt;&lt;/w:UseAsianBreakRules&gt;
   &lt;w:DontGrowAutofit&gt;&lt;/w:DontGrowAutofit&gt;
  &lt;/w:Compatibility&gt;
  &lt;w:BrowserLevel&gt;MicrosoftInternetExplorer4&lt;/w:BrowserLevel&gt;
 &lt;/w:WordDocument&gt;
&lt;/xml&gt;&lt;![endif]--&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;There are plenty of derby men and women who would willingly
tell you that Roller Derby has done no less than save their souls.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;This sport stirs a personal passion in so
many that is unrivaled in the sport world. Truly, Roller Derby often goes
beyond the track, and into the greater community, with teams participating in
charities, spearheading fundraisers and connecting families. These qualities
seem almost religious to me. And surely, the commitment, sacrifice,
selflessness and desire to better one’s self, are all virtues that span between
the church and rink. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;For our team, there is often a choice made between church
and skate.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Driving to practice one
Wednesday night, I saw the churches lit up, ready to accept those coming for
bible study.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Again on Sunday morning,
making my way to practice, I watched the parish parking lots filling and people
in their Sunday best, filing into the buildings of ivory and stained glass. For
me, there was no choice. Walking into the skating rink equals the feeling of
sanctuary that others feel when they step through the welcoming doors of their
local place of worship.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Lacing up and
hearing the rip of my Velcro as I put on my gear, is as close as I need to get
to prayer. My Sunday best usually consists of sweat wicking fabrics and a high
spandex content. And I couldn’t be more at peace. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;As an artist, whatever I’m living in my life has to find its
way out through my artwork eventually. So, as Roller Derby quickly took over, I
was filled with the need to express it on the page.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;There are plenty of good Roller Derby
centered artists in the world. The internet is littered with pin-up poses,
blood drenched bad-asses, freeze framed actions shots and every one with all
the right curves and none of the smelly funk of sweaty gear.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I tried to join this group, but try as I
might, I could not create one decent, strangely posed, scantily clad,
exceedingly voluptuous derby girl.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;I was
a failure.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;It was on one of the drives to practice, pondering in church
traffic, that I realized why I was having such a hard time.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Roller Derby
wasn’t some place I went to feel sexy. And while I play with some very fine
looking ladies, (Star City Roller Girls, rawr!) sex appeal is not the forefront
in any of our strategies.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;But devotion,
now that made sense to me. As surely as we worship the great derby players in
the world, we aspire to be as strong and talented as them. We give our bodies
and minds over to the sport and our teams. That made sense.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Roller Derby
didn’t need more pin-up art, it needed something tongue and cheek that spoke to
the passion that people felt about it. &lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;We needed our own, Passion of the Rink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal" align="center"&gt;&lt;img src="http://rollinnews.com/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f08%2ftwoskatescolored.jpg.axdx"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;So, the first Holy Roller Derby Saints were created and
slowly gained some followers. I was encouraged and warmed by the support I received
from other derby lovers I knew online. I realized I had found the connection
between my two loves, Art and Roller Derby.

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal" align="center"&gt;But then something terribly sad happened.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;A wonderful derby girl had a severe asthma
attack and tragically passed away. She ran a Fresh Meat group on Facebook,
where Freshies could vent, ask questions and share their triumphs. She was an inspiration and support to so many
of us around the world, myself included.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/span&gt;The outpouring of love, and the desire to honor her in the wake of this
tragedy spread quickly over the web, and the globe.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Then I was asked to make her the Patron Saint
of Fresh Meat. In my sadness, I jumped on the chance to do some small kindness for
a woman who had meant so much to so many, and created this:&lt;img src="http://rollinnews.com/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f08%2flouisacolored.jpg.axdx"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;This image has already been printed on buttons, t-shirts and stickers.
It’s being sold literally around the world in the US,
the UK, &lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;in Canada,
Australia, and Portugal to
just name a few and with all the proceeds going to our fallen derby girl’s family and a
charity in Louisa’s name. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;If you’d like to support this cause and remember Louisa you
can pick up a sticker here: &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;https://www.etsy.com/listing/184213947/large-4inch-and-small-2-inch-decal-for?ref=shop_home_active_1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;You can contact Lucid Lou at Twelve Thirty Five Skate Co. to
get a T-shirt with your donation going to the cause, by contacting her here: &lt;a href="http://www.twelvethirtyfourskateco.com/"&gt;http://www.twelvethirtyfourskateco.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;If you’d like to give directly to the fund for Louisa’s
family, please click this link: &lt;a href="http://www.gofundme.com/7vv3ig" target="_blank"&gt;http://www.gofundme.com/7vv3ig&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;Or if you'd like access to the hi-resolution version of the Patron Saint of Fresh Meat so you can start your own fundraising in Louisa's honor, contact me on my facebook page: www.facebook.com/meechermaker&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;While I was wish the Patron Saint of Fresh Meat never had to
be created, I feel honored to have my work supporting and remembering such a
passionate and kind Derby Player. Her Facebook Group will be kept going strong
and you can join us here: &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/rawmeatsydney/"&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/rawmeatsydney/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;As for the rest of my Derby Saints, they are happily growing
and showing up in color now.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;You can follow
my work on my Facebook page: &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/meechermaker"&gt;www.facebook.com/meechermaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;And find my work for sale in many awesome forms, (yes,
please, I DO need a Derby Saint mug and Hoodie!) at: &lt;a href="http://www.society6.com/meechermade"&gt;www.society6.com/meechermade&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;I'm working with some other derby girls and businesses to make the Derby Saints available as decals, t-shirts and possibly coloring books and water bottles. So follow my page to stay involved! The Derby Saints are just getting started. &lt;br&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;I’d love to continue to share my love of Roller Derby and
Art with the world. If you are looking for an image for charity, feel free to
contact me. I’m also readily accepting commissions, if you’re rethinking your
team logo, or want some cool merchandise for your team, talk to me. I can also alter
the existing Saints to fit your needs because I know you want to see the “Queen
of the Rink” in your team colors. I can also do private, personal commissions, because everyone wants to see their Derby Persona in stained glass. Feel free to contact me through my Facebook
page with any questions and ideas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;As always, I’m looking for your thoughts and comments.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;And do me a favor? At your next practice, hug every one of
your Derby Sisters and Brothers.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;You
wouldn’t be doing what you love without them there. Actually, take a moment
today to hug everyone you love. We are so busy running or skating around, we sometimes
forget how fleeting and precious life really is, and don’t always remember to
let people know how important to us they really are.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Make up for that today.&lt;span style="mso-spacerun:yes"&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;Be Derby
Strong. Spread the Derby
Love. And remember:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div align="center"&gt;&lt;img src="/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2f08%2fpackcolored.jpg.axdx"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>True</isdeleted>
  <bottomlineforconstribution />
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-04-08 09:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-04-08 13:13:17</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>meecher-mkr-roller-derby-as-religion-and-the-birth-of-derby-saints</slug>
  <tags>
    <tag>Charity</tag>
    <tag> Fundraising</tag>
    <tag>bout production</tag>
    <tag>derby art</tag>
    <tag>Derbylove</tag>
    <tag>saints</tag>
    <tag>Arts</tag>
    <tag>commission</tag>
    <tag>religion</tag>
    <tag>derby saints</tag>
    <tag>patron saint of fresh meat</tag>
    <tag>Fresh Meat</tag>
    <tag>merchandise</tag>
    <tag>team logos</tag>
  </tags>
  <comments />
  <categories>
    <category>d4d7bdde-a920-490b-8aaf-d7c4f57fd97e</category>
    <category>bdfcffd2-280b-45d2-9d88-66528177c6e9</category>
  </categories>
  <notifications />
</post>