<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="version">1.0A</string>
	<string name="ApplicationName">RDNation.Droid</string>
	<string name="home_welcome">Welcome to RDNation for Android.  We promise many more features, but wanted to showcase to the fans first.</string>
	<string name="some_title">Some Title</string>
	<string name="menu_string_search">Search</string>
	<string name="menu_string_up">up</string>
	<string name="menu_string_down">down</string>
	<string name="menu_string_left">left</string>
	<string name="menu_string_right">right</string>
	<string name="menu_string_refresh">refresh</string>
	<string name="menu_string_sort">Sort</string>
	<string name="gender_prompt">Select Gender</string>
	<string name="info_welcome">Welcome to RDNation for Android.  There are two full time developers behind RDNation and a few volunteer developers.  While we are doing our best, it is very hard for us to keep up with requests.  Just know that every single request will be acted on and executed on in some way or another.</string>
	<string name="info_feedback">
		<b>FEEDBACK:</b> If you have any comments/questions/concerns/feedback please feel free to just email us at info@rdnation.com.</string>
	<string name="info_games">
		<b>GAMES/SCORES:</b> Games and Scores provided by the RDNation Scoreboard.  If you want your game here, please just use the RDNation Scoreboard at your games.</string>
	<string name="info_events">
		<b>EVENTS:</b> Event Information provided by those Derby Leagues using RDNation as their calendar and event planning portal.</string>
	<string name="info_skaters">
		<b>SKATERS:</b> Skater information provided by those skaters who have created a profile on RDNation.  Attached Game data are for those skaters who have used the RDNation scoreboard at bouts.</string>
	<string name="info_leagues">
		<b>LEAGUES:</b> League information provided by leagues whom have signed up to RDNation.</string>
	<string name="info_shops">
		<b>SHOPS:</b> RDNation has shops where you can personally buy and sell derby merchandise and been seen by thousands of derby people world wide.</string>
	<string-array name="gender_array">
		<item>Male</item>
		<item>Female</item>
	</string-array>
	<string name="position_prompt">Select Position</string>
	<string-array name="position_array">
		<item>Owner Of a Team/League</item>
		<item>A Skater</item>
		<item>Owner of a Federation</item>
		<item>Referee</item>
		<item>Non Skating Official</item>
		<item>Other</item>
	</string-array>
	
</resources>
